PÉTER JÓZSA

FULL STACK DEVELOPER





CODECOOL

Contact

jozsa.peter88@gmail.com

+36202914145

www.linkedin.com/in/

peteriozsa98/

github.com/jozsapeter88

Self Definition

I'm a driven and ambitious person with a strong passion for technology and a desire to set foot in the IT industry. During my studies at Codecool, I had the opportunity to gain valuable experience in teamwork and collaboration. Working closely with my peers and mentors, I actively engaged in group projects that required effective communication, coordination, and problemsolving skills. Outside of my professional pursuits, you can often find me actively participating in various sports activities and following the world of technological advances.

Strength

I have experience in developing full-stack applications and I love expressing my creativity through the process. I also have experience in Git version control, Docker, CI/CD and databases. Communication and teamwork are strong suits of mine, and I welcome constructive criticism as an opportunity for growth. Continuously learning and staying updated with industry advancements are essential to me.

Mentor Opinion

"Péter consistently delivered a good quality work during his time at Codecool. He is willing to ask questions and open for feedback to improve his skills. He is extremely reliable: have not even been late once during his entire year. His teammates enjoy working with him. He will be a solid member of any software developer team as a junior, and will grow rapidly to medior level."

- Kornél Regius, mentor



Hard Skills





























Recent Projects

STOCK MANAGEMENT SYSTEM

https://github.com/jozsapeter88/stock-manager

A React/C# project that helps manage facilities and track their corresponding item stock.

NFWSWHI7

https://github.com/jozsapeter88/NewsWhiz

A full-stack application helping the user extracting news articles, saving and editing its contents.

PERSONAL PORTFOLIO

https://github.com/jozsapeter88/personal-portfolio

A site made to introduce myself, highlight my works and practice my CSS(Sass)

Work Experience

Customer Service Associate (2019 - 2020) — MediaMarkt Magyarország

Freelancer Translator (2017 - 2023) — Translator

Education

Mechatronics preparatory training (2013 - 2017) — DSZC Brassai Sámuel Grammar School and Technical High School

Mechatronics trechnician training (2017 - 2018) — DSZC Brassai Sámuel Grammar School and Technical High School

BA in English and American Studies (2018 - 2021) — University of Debrecen

Full-Stack Development Course (2022 - 2023) — Codecool

Spoken Languages

English — Advanced Spanish — Intermediate